As Prophet T.B. Joshua touches the people one by one, praying for them in Jesus' name,
the Spirit of God exposes this man.
Who are you?
I am a lion.
You are a lion?
Yes.
How many powers do you have?
I have many powers.
I gave him many powers.
Move like a lion!
He has a scorpion on his body.
Where?
It is here.
I want to kill this boy.
These are the powers – one here and one here.
This is a scorpion; if he hits you, you will fall down and die.
This is a scorpion.
If this guy gets angry…
I gave him the spirit of smoking but T.B. Joshua told him not to smoke again.
If I enter his dreams, Prophet T.B. Joshua will take the cigarette from my hand.
This place swells up.
When he gets angry - what happens?
If he gets angry and he hits you with this hand, you will die.
He has hit uncountable people.
I sent him to Europe.
This one, if he wants a woman, any woman he likes, if he touches her, she will fall for him.
After the woman has fallen for him and he has enjoyed her, I will send her away.
What did you do to his marriage?
This one is not married.
He doesn't want to be married.
We gave him a wife but he did not want her.
He said he wanted a foolish girl who gave him two children – a boy and a girl.
I chased all of them away.
This is the family mark.
With this mark, anywhere he goes, I follow him.
Who is he?
How did you enter him?!
His grandfather gave him to me.
I am much older than you.
You are still young.
I am 1,500 years old.
T.B. Joshua is everywhere, even in his room – why?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Prayer & Deliverance In Jesus' Name
This boy is your friend; I am not your friend.
This boy loves you; if anybody wants to argue about it, he will chase the person away.
Deliverance continues, as Prophet T.B. Joshua touches him again with the lightening power of God,
in Jesus' name.
He shocked me with electricity; it went in here and out here.
:)
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
With the final touch of light from the throne of grace, the spiritual battle between light and darkness,
in the life of this man comes to an end, as the darkness is expelled in Jesus' Christ name.
Thank You, Jesus Christ for setting this captive free.
TESTIMONY TIME
Right now, you can see on the screen of your TV that gentleman concerned is overcome by emotions
after what he has just witnessed.
This is the clear proof that what we saw just now was not him -
it was the evil spirit within him that was confessing.
Today, he is delivered, to the glory of God.
This is the reason we are seeing these tears as an evidence that indeed at that moment
it was that evil spirit that was speaking and working through him.
Right now, he is free and he is here to give his confession and testimony, to the glory of God.
Brother, we understand your emotions - we just ask that you calm down, prepare yourself,
so that you can share this testimony, so people of God can learn and glory can be given to God
and shame to the devil.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Muyideen Shittu.
Mr Muyideen Shittu
Nigerian Living In Ghana
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Muyideen Shittu.
I am a Nigerian but I live in Ghana.
My father is Nigerian.
He is one of the powerful men in Nigeria.
He was called 'Red Scorpion'.
Some people might know my father.
My story goes like this: when I was young, my father loved me so much
because I have plenty sisters – 48 sisters.
So, he put a scorpion tattoo on my arm and told me that anywhere I was,
no one born of a woman could destroy me.
I put that idea in my head – I had power.
Now, I want to confess my sins because I know everything is over.
Prophet T.B. Joshua saved my life because I had sold my life to the devil
but Prophet T.B. Joshua brought me back home.
Mr Muyideen Shittu
Deliverance Testimony
At the beginning, I was a drug dealer and human trafficker.
I had connections and links everywhere.
I did it for many years.
As I was growing up, I was rejected by every teacher and headmaster in school because I always liked fighting.
I could fight 20 to 30 people but nobody could defeat me.
I knew where I belonged but now, I belong to Jesus.
So, you grew up with the strong spirit of anger, fighting and when you became older
you wanted to travel abroad.
Tell us what happened.
I didn't respect anybody.
Whether they had money, power or whether the person was holding a gun, I didn't respect them.
I only believed in myself.
My father told me that I must believe in myself, that nothing would happen to me
as long as the scorpion tattoo was on me and I believed in myself.
Mr Muyideen Shittu
Deliverance Testimony
I travelled to many countries and saw many things.
I know that there are some people who are watching me - maybe I did either one business or the other with them -
I just ask God to forgive me because I was involved in drug dealing and human trafficking.
I had some elderly people who were my buyers – they were aged between 65 and 70.
I would ask them whether they needed young ladies to massage their bodies.
When they agreed, I would negotiate with the ladies, telling them that after staying two years with the men,
they should ensure that the men willed their properties to them.
After they collected all the men properties, I would share 50/50 with them.
However, there was one case that caused a problem.
The man was my closest friend; at the end of the day, he said I tricked him and he sent mafia to me.
The mafia told me, "CK, they didn't tell us that it was you. A man reported you to us".
I told them to forget about him.
After that, he came back with another mafia group who exchanged bullets with me.
I was shot on the chest.
I also shot the man.
At the end, my neighbour called the police and I was taken to the hospital.
I was later sentenced to three years imprisonment while the man was sentenced to 20 years.
I levelled on allegations against him, saying that he slept with children.
When I left prison, I headed to Germany.
OK. So, you were imprisoned in Italy over this issue, and from Italian prison you went to Germany.
When I got to Germany, I started my business again.
At that time, I joined human trafficking, matching men with women.
If the women wanted men for marriage, they usually paid four thousand euros
while I searched for the men who would marry them.
I worked with big men who would marry them and later divorce after three weeks.
I would then take 2,000 euros and the man would take the rest.
Furthermore, I would also approach the crippled to be my customers.
I would tell them that I had husbands for them and I would take money from both them and their "husbands".
When they get married, I would warn the man that if after three months,
he did not leave the woman, I would deal with him.
After three months, the man would leave the cripple and she would come back telling me her husband had left.
I would tell them to bring me more money so that I would look for other husbands for them.
I went to the US and met another gang.
I lived in California but had another house in Orlando where I operated from.
In the US, I met a lady from Norway; she didn't know that I was dealing in drugs.
She always asked me why people kept bringing money to me.
I told her my father was a king in Africa dealing in gold and that he always sent me money.
She was convinced with my lies.
One day, I received a consignment of drugs which I brought to the house.
The lady had thought it was money but I told her it was not.
Out of curiosity, she tore the bag and found cocaine powder inside.
She called her friend and her friend told her it was cocaine.
She was shocked and while I turned to go to the room, she ran away.
I later tore every cocaine bag I had into the toilet and flushed them away.
They finally found out that I was selling drugs.
So, I had to come back home.
In 2012, I was sitting on my bed tuning my TV channels and I saw Emmanuel TV.
Then I didn’t appreciate the value of Emmanuel TV.
Sir, to the glory of God, we just want to talk about the deliverance you received here last week.
How did you receive your deliverance and what are the changes in your life after the deliverance?
The only thing I can remember about my deliverance is that I came in front of
the man of God and he touched me.
I don’t remember the rest.
I don’t even remember who took off my clothes.
I don’t remember anything.
I just found myself naked.
So, you just remember the man of God touching you, and that's all?
Yes. I don’t remember anything.
Ever since the deliverance, you received last week - can you tell us the changes you've seen in your life?
After the deliverance, for three days, I've been having the same dream.
In the dream, I saw people beat me.
Immediately they slapped my face, the man of God came and everybody ran away.
So, I asked the man of God why he did not come on time lest they killed me.
The man of God answered me saying that I was still keeping those people in my mind
and that was why they could beat me.
He then prayed for me in the dream again.
He also told me that whenever I want to sleep, I should say,
"Lord Jesus, I leave my soul to You. Save me and guide me."
That was the prayer the man of God gave me in my dream.
Mr Muyideen Shittu
Deliverance Testimony
Since then, I pray that prayer twice before going to bed and I've not seen those people in my dreams again.
The evil spirit within me manifested and made me remove my clothes.
The evil spirit removed everything it had deposited in me and left.
I did not want the power which belonged to the evil spirit anymore.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God for our brother's deliverance.
We believe all we have heard from him is enough of a valuable lesson for us - people of God -
especially young people around the world.
Today, he is delivered, freed from his past life.
Satan has used him to destroy so many people.
He is a living testimony, to the glory of God.
Brother, we pray that God will give you the grace to maintain this deliverance, by making the Word of God
the standard for your life.
And we know as you do so, the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.